gawab.com 2006-10-16

# Gawab.com 4,627,530 Users Can't Be Wrong!

This Privacy Policy applies to the collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by Gawab.com. If there are any exceptions, Gawab.com will clearly state them prior to collecting any information. Please be aware that, as part of the Services, Gawab.com provides links to Web sites operated by third parties, and also provides co-branded web-based email services to third parties for display on their own Web sites. Gawab.com is not responsible for information collection, privacy practices or content of those third party Web sites or applications. 

Gawab.com is committed to protecting your privacy. To ensure that you,as a registered user of Gawab.com, receive top performance without compromising your security and confidentiality, we are committed to the following: 

**We will limit the collection and use of customer information to the minimum required for us to deliver superior service to you..** Gawab.com will explicitly ask for information that personally identifies you (Personal Information), such as your first and last name, country and postal code, gender, date of birth, occupation, and alternative contact email address or phone number. You may update this information at any time from within your Gawab.com account. 

**We will always maintain control over the confidentiality of our customer information.** Your Personal Information is used solely for the purpose of identifying, managing demographic statistics and to display appropriate individualized advertisements. Gawab.com keeps all of your Personal Information private and does not share it with any third parties.Gawab.com will not disclose any of your Personal Information unless such action is necessary to : 

  * Conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process. 
  * Protect and defend the rights or property of Gawab.com. 
  * Enforce Gawab.com Terms of Service. 
  * Act to protect the interests of its members or others. 

Please be aware that when you click on the advertising powered by Gawab.com, you may be linked to sites that are not operated by Gawab.com. Gawab.com assumes no responsibility for the collection or use of any information that you provide to such sites.We strongly recommend that you review the privacy policy statements of all sites that collect information from you. 

**You will be notified of any changes in our “personal information” collection processes, the way we use that information or our privacy policy itself.** If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change. 

**We ensure subscribers’ privacy.** To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, Gawab.com has considered procedures to safeguard and secure subscriber’s confidentiality. We consider our customers' mailboxes andthe content of all messages to be private. We do not monitor or disclose email messages unless we believe we must do so: 

  * To enforce our email Terms and Conditions, 
  * Because we are required to do so by law, or 
  * To defend Gawab.com in any legal action or to protect the property of Gawab.com 

Additionally, our subscribers must agree to respect the privacy and confidentiality of others. Since privacy is, in part, a function of our customers' passwords, we encourage them to change their passwords frequently and to not share them with anyone. 

**We use Cookies to collect statistical information.** Please be aware that banner ads on Gawab.com may collect cookies as part of the process of serving those ads. These cookies are typically used for the purpose of tracking performance of the banner ads. Gawab.com and/orits advertisers may collect information about online behavior using these cookies. These cookies might contain identification information that enables us to see how our users are interacting with our site andhow frequently they are returning . Gawab.com may share information about you and your usage of our Services with third parties. 

**We are serious about your privacy.** Gawab.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. By using our services, you signify your assent to the terms and conditions. If you do not agree, please do not use this site. By selecting the "I Accept" button and submitting the enrollment form you agree that you have viewed and understand the Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy presented to you and that you agree to abide by all conditions set forth in the agreement. 

Gawab.com respects all users and their privacy. It is our policy to comply with internationally recognized standards of personal data privacy protection. 

If at any time you believe that Gawab.com has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by email at support@gawab.com and we will use all reasonable efforts to promptly determine and correct the problem.
